bucksense.com 2019-12-27

# In-house marketing, done right | Bucksense

﻿ 

## INTRODUCTION

This Privacy Policy explains how Bucksense, Inc. (" **Bucksense** " or " **us** " or “ **we** ”) collects, uses, and shares information from and about you when you interact with a mobile application or website that displays Bucksense advertisements (“ **Bucksense Ad Platform** ”or “ **Platform** ” or “ **Service** ”).

Bucksense serves advertisements to end users of various publishers (such as website operators or mobile app developers), via real-time marketplace platforms exchanges (" **Exchanges** ") and/or such publishers. Those ads are provided by advertisers, who use **Platform** to serve their ads and manage the overall performance of their ad campaigns, including by using third party services that integrate with our Platform. When an end user receives or clicks on an ad, we might receive or collect some or all of the data provided below, whether from the end user's device, from the relevant Exchange/s, from third parties and/or publishers (" **Data** ").

We generally do not collect or use personal information about individual users through the Bucksense Service. When we say “ **Personal Information** ”, we mean individually identifiable information that would allow us to determine the actual identity of and/or directly contact a specific living person, such as an email address or telephone number. We collect personal information only when we are contacted directly by an individual through the our site and the individual voluntarily provides personal information to us, such as by submitting a question or registering to use the Bucksense Service. Bucksense does not collect Personal Information about consumers that receive advertiser offers through the Bucksense Service.

_You are not legally obligated to provide us any Data. If you do not want Platform to collect such Data, please follow the instructions below toOpt-Out._

You can find a list of Bucksense’s partners here **[www.bucksense.com/about-us/#ourPartners](https://www.bucksense.com/about-us/#ourPartners)**

## COLLECTION OF DATA

The Bucksense Services collect information about your device and the ads that we deliver onto your device. This data, which is collected passively using various technologies may come from such sources as your web browser or the apps that you use. We also may obtain the precise location (e.g., lat/long coordinates) of your device and may use that information to deliver targeted ads. We may also combine the information collected across multiple sites and mobile apps in order to create interest segments that help us target future advertisements based upon those inferred interests. This practice is sometimes referred to as behavioral advertising or interest-based advertising. We use this information as part of the Bucksense Services to perform a variety of tasks, such as limiting the number of times a specific advertisement is presented to the same user (frequency capping), providing an advertisement to only certain types of users, or providing a report to a client on the number of its advertisements that were clicked. We may share this information with clients, vendors, and other companies that we conduct business with as permitted by law.

When we present an ad on your device we might receive or collect some or all of the following:

  * Which application will present the ad
  * If you clicked the ad and when
  * IP address
  * User Agent
  * Carrier where applicable
  * General location (i.e. city or zipcode)
  * Android advertising ID or Apple advertising ID (IDFA) as applicable

In operating the Bucksense Service we may use the following technologies:

  * **Cookies** are small data files containing a string of characters, such as unique browser identifiers. Cookies are stored on your computer or other device and act as unique tags that identify your browser. Bucksense or our Clients and Partners may deploy a cookie on your browser when you click on the ad banner. This technology may provide with information regarding your IP address, browser type, the web pages that you visit just before or after visiting a website, the web pages viewed, and the dates and times of your visits. 
  * A **pixel tag** (also commonly known as a web beacon or clear GIF) is an invisible 1 x 1 pixel that is placed on certain web pages. When you access a web page with a pixel tag, the pixel tag may generate a generic notice of the visit, and permit us, or our Clients or Partners, to set or read cookies. Pixel tags are used in combination with cookies to track the activity on a website by a particular browser on a particular device. If you disable cookies, pixel tags simply detect a given website visit. We or our Clients and Partners, may use cookies to, for example, remember you, track trends, and collect information about how you use Clients’ or Partners’ websites or interact with advertising. We, and our Clients and Partners, use cookies to provide relevant content to you and replace non-relevant ads with ads that better match your interests.
  * **Mobile Device Identifiers and SDKs**. We, or our Clients or Partners, may use mobile SDKs to collect information, such as Mobile IDs, and information related to how mobile devices and their users interact with our Bucksense ad services and those using our Bucksense ad services. The SDK is computer code that app developers can include in their apps to enable ads to be shown, data to be collected, and other related services to be implemented. Sometimes, we obtain data through other interfaces that deliver similar data to us, which are commonly referred to as APIs. We may use these technologies, for example, to analyze or measure certain advertising through apps and browsers based on information associated with your mobile device.If you would like to opt out from having ads tailored to you in this way on your mobile device, please follow the Opt-Out paragraph. Our clients or partners may use the above technologies (sometimes, in combination with each other or other data such as IP addresses or hashed or de-identified data files) to coordinate identifiers across platforms, browsers, or devices, in order to more efficiently analyze or target advertising.

**CHILDREN:** We do not knowingly or intentionally collect any Data about children under the age of 16. If you believe that information about your child under the age of 16 may have been provided to Bucksense and/or collected by Platform, please contact us at [privacy@bucksense.com](mailto:privacy@bucksense.com).

## HOW BUCKSENSE COLLECTS THE DATA

The Data may be provided to us directly by you, by the relevant Exchange/s and/or by publishers.

We may also receive device identifiers such as Apple’s IFA (Identifier for Advertisers), Google’s Advertising Identifier (AID), and/or similar information from other third parties – in order to serve ads on behalf of our advertisers to the end users specified in such information. The collection and use of such information by the respective third parties is governed by the privacy policies of such third parties and by applicable law. Our use of such information is governed by this privacy policy, and the end users' consent and preferences as conveyed to us by such end users, by publishers and by other third parties.

## HOW BUCKSENSE USES AND MANTAIN THE DATA

Bucksense uses the Data to provide end users with our advertisers' customized ads regarding content and/or apps, to enable our advertisers to analyze their ad campaigns and performance (including via their respective tools and partners), and in order to improve the overall quality of Bucksense's services. 

## HOW LONG BUCKSENSE KEEPS THE DATA

Bucksense may retain and use the Data **for up to 90 days following** the collection and/or receipt thereof, in order to ensure the proper performance of its services, and to allow its advertisers to properly manage and analyze their ad campaigns via our Platform.

In some cases we might retain certain Data for a longer period, as reasonably necessary to comply with an **Opt-Out request** and/or with any applicable laws, or if we believe in good faith that the Data might be necessary in the future for dispute resolution purposes.

Bucksense may use non-personal aggregated information, including such that was derived from Data but anonymized or pseudonymized to remove its personally identifying characteristics (" **Aggregated Data** "), including for statistical purposes. Aggregated Data may be kept indefinitely.

Bucksense will not sell, trade or rent Data, excluding Aggregated Data, to any third party unless we have the end user's prior consent.

## HOW BUCKSENSE SHARING AND DISCLOSURE THE DATA

However, Bucksense may provide the identity of an end user to third parties and/or disclose Data to third parties if it believes in good faith that such identification or disclosure are necessary to:

  1. facilitate compliance with any law regulation or other governmental authority, including, for example, compliance with a court order or subpoena, or
  2. protect the safety or security of any person or property, including Platform, or
  3. protect Bucksense's legitimate interests in any legal or other disputes.

_Bucksense may also disclose the Data:_

  1. _third parties helping to provide and maintain Platform;_
  2. the relevant advertiser(s);
  3. upon a transfer or sale to another entity of all or substantially all of Bucksense’s stock or assets; (d) upon any bankruptcy or other corporate reorganization.

Bucksense may also share Data with its service providers, such as cloud hosting providers and data security and fraud prevention services, in order to properly facilitate and provide Platform.

## ADS, APPS AND OTHER THIRD PARTY CONTENT

Our Platform and ads served via our Platform may provide links to certain third party websites or referrals to certain third parties' products or services. If you choose to visit a third party's website or use its products or services, please be aware that Bucksense does not endorse and cannot ensure that you will be satisfied with any such products or services, and that the third party's privacy policy will govern your activities and any Data they collect about you and/or you disclose while interacting with such third party.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to websites, ads, applications or services other than our Platform, even if Bucksense's services are embedded/linked in/to such, or to websites, ads, apps or services that are not expressly and officially provided by Bucksense. Please be aware that opting out of our Platform does not necessarily imply that you are opting out of any publisher's website, ad hosting app/website or any other third party's website and/or services.

## RIGHTS OF THE DATA SUBJECT

The end user has the right to access, rectify, right to object, claim, block about its data:

  * You have the right to request information about whether and which personal data is processed by our company.
  * You also have the right to demand that your personal data is rectified or amended.
  * Under certain circumstances, you have the right to request that your personal data should be deleted.
  * Under certain circumstances, you have the right to demand that the processing of your personal data should be restricted.
  * You can withdraw your consent to the processing and use of your data completely or partially at any time with future application.
  * You have the right to obtain your personal data in a common, structured and mechanically readable format.
  * If you have any questions, comments, complaints or requests in connection with our statement on data protection and the processing of your personal data, you can also contact our data protection officer in detail.
  * If you have any questions, comments, complaints or requests in connection with our statement on data protection and the processing of your personal data, you can also contact our data protection officer in detail.

Please email us at [privacy@bucksense.com](mailto:privacy@bucksense.com) or adress indicated below, we will reply within 30 days.  
It is possible that you will be asked for a contribution, but only if your requests are manifestly unfounded or excessive.  
We may request a photocopy of your identity document to ensure your identity. 

## CHOICE/OPT-OUT

We use the information we collect on the Bucksense Ad Platform to serve you with interest-based ads based on your inferred interests, preferences and location.

  * _On your browser:_ If you prefer not to receive ads that are tailored to your interests, you can opt out of the Bucksense Ad Platform using information to provide you interest-based ads at any time by clicking here:  
This opt-out requires that you have cookies enabled and will need to be repeated if cookies are cleared on your browser (which can happen if you clear your browsing history or re-install your browser).
  * _On your mobile device:_ You can also usually opt out of the receipt of all in-app interest-based ads by using your device’s privacy settings. Each operating system (e.g., iOS, Android) provides its own instructions on how to prevent the delivery of such in-app ads:  

    * For iOS, instructions can be found here: <https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT202074>
    * For Android Devices:  
Open Settings  
Select Accounts and/or select Sync (this can vary, depending on your device)  
Select Google  
Select Privacy and/or Select Ads (this can vary, depending on your device)  
Click on “opt-out of interest-based ads”.
    * For other operating systems, please review the support materials and/or the privacy settings for your device’s operating system in order to opt-out of interest-based in-app ads.

Please note that if you opt out of Bucksense Ad Platform using your information for interest-based advertising you may still receive “generic” ads from us that are not based on your inferred interests.

## DATA PROTECTION

We have taken extensive technical and organisational measures to secure your data against potential risks, such as unauthorised login or access, unauthorised perusal, amendment or distribution, as well as against loss, deletion or misuse.

In order to protect your personal data against unauthorised access by third parties when being transmitted, we secure data transmissions, if necessary, using **SSL encryption**.  
This is a standard encryption procedure for online services, particularly for the Internet.

## DATA TRANSFER TO THIRD COUNTRIES

In order to process and store the data we collect, this Data is sometimes transferred to countries outside the European Union, this is done on the basis of contractual regulations stipulated by law that ensure appropriate protection of your data.

## CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY

Bucksense reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy regularly for any changes.

## CONTACT INFORMATION

If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy practices, you may contact us:  
Bucksense Inc.  
119 W 24th Street, 4th Floor, New York, NY 10011
